Police got out of the car, gave multiple warnings, and shot him when he was outside of the car.
It was only until Azari's family attorney came forward with neighborhood surveillance video
showing very clearly that Azari never even exited the car.
And when they did a search of that car, they actually didn't even find any gun.
They found two knives.
So it was very clear that there was some sort of distrust that just immediately comes with that community
because it was such a different story than what police had initially put out there.
But again, what we see in those two videos are not...
So let me just tell you all how the media really playing on our top right now, right?
Because I got the video.
Good thing I was watching CNN when they played it
because I actually waited to see if any of these major platforms,
Shade Room, Miss Onsite, blah, blah, blah, all of that shit that we be looking at, everything.
I wanted to see if anybody was going to post it, if we was going to see it.
So let me tell you all how the media going to play on y'all top, right?
Because they don't want y'all to see it.
They don't want y'all to know that they still doing this shit in the way that they doing it.
Y'all heard the lady say the police lied and said that this man got out of his car and lunged at them
and was threatening them from outside the car and that's why they shot him.
But if it wasn't for the neighborhood showing video that he never even got out of the car,
then they would have let this shit slide.
So I'm going to show y'all the video.
I'm just warning y'all.
It's going to piss you off.
Here you go to warning.
If you don't want to see it, keep scrolling, but it's going to piss you off.
How the fuck is this not plastered every fucking wear right now?
You want to know why?
Because the media as a whole has collectively decided to not make this a forefront
because they don't want us to go out there and do what we do best.
They don't want us to protest.
They don't want us to step.
They don't want us to get on a motherfucking next because what?
How?
Never got out the car.
You shot this man through a closed fucking window.
Five seconds.
Within five seconds.
So because they don't, they don't want to tell y'all, they don't want to tell y'all what they did.
They don't want y'all to know.
I'm going to be the one to tell it because y'all got, y'all got like fucked up.
Y'all got like fucked up.
And the parents, the family was like, they didn't even want it censored.
They like, no, release the video.
Release the real video.
Release exactly what happened.
And that wasn't even the full video.
That's what CNN, after they watched the entire thing,
that's what they picked apart and decided to play because it was so, it was so graphic.
They knew it was going to upset so many people that they could only,
that's all that they could give you.
These police lied and said that this man was out of the car, threatening them.
They lied and they were going to roll with that lie until a month later
when the family got footage from the neighborhood.
But we supposed to trust y'all.